{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Allen_(playwright)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Coronation_Street",
    "human_readable": "Jim Allen was a notable work in Coronation Street.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9602609276771545,
            "question": "What role did Jim Allen play on Coronation Street?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816234290599823,
            "question": "Was Jim Allen a notable actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.691216766834259,
            "question": "Who was Jim Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6046021580696106,
            "question": "What was Jim Allen known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4498046338558197,
            "question": "Where might you have seen Jim Allen perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43193602561950684,
            "question": "Was Jim Allen involved in a famous soap opera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4154709577560425,
            "question": "In what television show did Jim Allen appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3819810450077057,
            "question": "What is Coronation Street about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11642090976238251,
            "question": "Is Coronation Street a long-running TV show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.011546051129698753,
            "question": "Can you name any popular soap operas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Allen was a notable work in Coronation Street.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8178_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Coronation Street a long-running TV show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8178_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Coronation Street about?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8178_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what television show did Jim Allen appear?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8178_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8178_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\n*  The provided text documents clearly state that Jim Allen wrote 36 episodes of *Coronation Street*. This directly supports the statement that he was a notable work in *Coronation Street*. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "To evaluate whether the information in the documents supports the triple, I will check if Jim Allen was indeed a notable writer for Coronation Street.\n\nUpon reviewing the provided context information, I found that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8178/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt, it is mentioned that Jim Allen wrote 36 episodes of Coronation Street between January 1965 and September 1967.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8178/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt, it is stated that Jim Allen also wrote three episodes for the show in August 1996.\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple, indicating that Jim Allen was indeed a notable writer for Coronation Street.\n\nThe final answer is:\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jim Allen was a notable writer for Coronation Street.\" Specifically, the document at file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8178/re-ranker-msmarco/5.txt` mentions that Jim Allen wrote 36 episodes of Coronation Street between January 1965 and September 1967, and the document at file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8178/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt` also notes that Allen had an idea for his first major play based on his experience writing for the show."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}